CONTROL  no contention      -> ledger now {'a': 1}   (must be {'a': 1})
TEST     with a live holder -> _save raised: None
         ledger content after the write: {}
         the increment was LOST silently: True
         temp files left behind: []

VERDICT X5b: CONFIRMED тАФ on Windows a live handle on the ledger makes os.replace raise, the except swallows it, the temp file is deleted, and the delivery/rotation state is DISCARDED WITH NO WARNING. The author's stated harm ('over-delivers AND lets the next save write a nearly-empty ledger over a good one') is still reachable here, by a different mechanism than the one the atomic write was added to close.
